人人影视
原创翻译  双语字幕
字幕组招新中
请访问 YYSubs.com
翻译    四畹饭  silvaliao  mumu点心  易碎的绝对
翻译    王木木  leonyyyyy  Lark_Song  苏葵
校对    苏葵
时间轴    Jessie 噃噃
后期    拉图
总监    苏葵
以圣父
In the name of the Father,
圣子和圣灵的名义
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
原谅我  神父  我有罪
Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
距离我上次忏悔已经一天了
It's been one day since my last confession.
以下是我的罪过
These are my sins.
我一直在生我妹妹的气
I've been angry at my sister.
我没有念念珠
I failed to pray the rosary.
我在药店排队时
I got really mad
发了很大的脾气
in line at the drug store.
...以圣子和圣灵的名义
...Son, the Holy Spirit.
距离我上次忏悔已经过去一个月了
It's been a month since my last confession.
以下是我的罪过
These are my sins.
我讨厌我的丈夫
I hate my husband.
他老是把脏盘子放在水槽里
He puts dishes in the sink
尽管我跟他说过无数次
even when I've told him 100 times
要把它们放在洗碗机里
to put them in the dishwasher.
然后他也不倒垃圾
Then he doesn't take out the garbage.
他觉得这是女人的工作
He thinks it's women's work.
请问  有什么不是女人的工作
Well, what isn't women's work?
欢迎参加早上6点的弥撒
Welcome to the 6:00 a.M. Mass.
我们像往常一样开始吧
Let us begin as we always do.
以圣父
In the name of the Father,
圣子和圣灵的名义
the Son, Holy Spirit.
阿门
Amen.
谁
Hello?
你好
Hello.
你有什么事吗
May I help you?
你认得我吗
Do you recognize me?
维克托·莱孔特
Victor LeConte?
你知道我是做什么的吗
Do you know what I do?
你是梵蒂冈特勤局的
You work with the Vatican Secret Service.
"圣体"
The Entity.
根本不存在圣体  大卫
There is no Entity, David.
只不过是...梵蒂冈的朋友们
There are merely... friends of the Vatican.
有些是大使  有些是教区牧师
Some are ambassadors, some parish priests.
有些在情报部门工作
Some work in intelligence--
中央情报局  军情六处  对外安全总局
the CIA, MI6, DGSE.
他们提供信息和帮助
They offer information and assistance.
就这样  没什么神秘之处
That's all. There's nothing mysterious about it.
这是关于RSM育儿机构吗
Is this about RSM Fertility?
我有个问题要问你  大卫
I have a question for you, David.
你不打算回答我的问题吗
You're not going to answer my question.
你的问题无关紧要
Your question is irrelevant.
你为什么当牧师
Why are you a priest?
为上帝服务
To serve God.
那是什么
What is that?
你的个人资料
Your profile.
你认为你在这里是在侍奉上帝吗
And do you believe that you are serving God here?
我不清楚
I don't know.
我不知道上帝需要什么
I don't know what God wants.
如果我知道上帝想要什么  你会意外吗
Would it surprise you to learn that I do know what God wants?
会
Yes.
上帝希望你成为梵蒂冈的朋友
God wants you to be a friend of the Vatican.
那...我该怎么做呢
And... how do I do that?
说你愿意
Say yes.
愿意什么
To?
你想为世界做好事
You want to do good in the world.
你想对抗邪恶
You want to fight evil.
但你在这里深感无聊
And yet you're bored here.
你在生自己的气  因为你厌倦了
And you're angry at yourself for being bored.
但你看不出
But you can't see the connection
所有这些没人参加的弥撒
between all of these poorly-attended masses,
所有这些忏悔
all these confessions
和世上的邪恶之间有什么联系
and the evil in the world.
你在监视我吗
You're watching me?
我们用不着监视你
We don't need to watch you.
纽约发生了一些邪恶的事情
There's something happening in New York that is evil.
作为一个评估者  你看到了
As an assessor, you see it.
但这不仅仅是超自然现象
But it is not just supernatural.
它也是有形的
It is also corporeal.
下周某个时候你会接到一个电话
You will receive a call sometime in the next week,
要求你执行一项任务
asking you to perform a task.
什么任务
What task?
你会知道它来自梵蒂冈
You will know that it is from the Vatican
因为它会有这样一句话
because it will be preceded by this phrase:
"主之意志"
"Is est a Deo habetur."
"这是上帝的意志"
"And it is deemed by God."
你必须毫无异议地执行此任务
You must perform this task without question
明白吗
do you understand?
你在招募我吗
You're recruiting me?
我需要你说愿意
I need you to say yes.
我要告诉大主教
I need to tell the Monsignor.
不行
No.
跟你聊天很开心
It was good to talk to you.
等等
Wait.
你想我说愿意吗
You want a yes?
是的
Yes.
如果你答应了  就不能告诉任何人
And if you say yes, you cannot tell anyone.
不能告诉大主教
Not the Monsignor,
也不能告诉你的修女朋友和你的世俗伙伴
not your nun friend, none of your secular associates.
如果你同意  你就是梵蒂冈的朋友
If you say yes, you will be a friend of the Vatican.
这是个重任
And that is a burden.
但没人逼你回答
But no one is forcing you to respond.
你自己决定
That is up to you.
我做了一点调查
So I did a little research,
再加一间卧室
and to add one more bedroom,
总共要8万美元
it would be 80,000, all in.
再加上浴室呢
And the bathroom?
再加9万
Separate, 90,000.
还要9万
Another 90?
我们应该以八万五千美元的价格卖掉
We're supposed to be selling the trekking business
徒步旅行业务
for $85,000.
我们还欠...抵押贷款8万
And we still owe... 80,000 on the mortgage.
好吧  那...
Okay, so...
我只要找一份工资
well, I just have to try and get a job that pays
在7.5万左右的工作就行了吧
what, in the range of 75,000?
我的工资是6万  但是
My job pays 60,000, but...
它还支付了孩子们一半的学费
it also pays for half the kids' tuition
和我们的医疗费用
and our health care.
我们可以把孩子送到公立学校来省钱
We could save by sending the kids to public school.
劳拉  拜托
Laura, please!
妈妈  公立学校
Mom, they have bomb threats
-有炸弹威胁  -别这么夸张
- at the public school. - Don't be melodramatic.
-她没夸张  是真的  -妈妈  水槽又堵了
- She's not. It's true. - Mom, the sink is clogged again.
别碰它
Don't touch it.
-妈  我想要自己的房间  -你要自己的房间
- Mom, I want my own room. - You want your own room?
孩子们  孩子们
Guys, guys,
guys, guys!
除非你们能在煤矿场找到工作
Unless you girls get jobs in the coal mines,
这间卧室是给你爸妈住的
this is one for your parents.
-好吗  好  -那算了吧
- Okay? Okay. - I'm gonna pass on that.
-好了  上楼去  -你们总是拒绝我们的一切要求
- Okay, go upstairs. - You say no to everything.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Good night, now.
我不...我们可以...
So I don't... do we just...
可以直接雇一个承包商来做吗
do we just hire a contractor and start in?
嗯  得先拿到贷款
Yeah, we got to get the loans first.
-这些钱用来干什么  -那是我妈妈
- What about these earnings? - Oh, that's my mom
-想在车库上花的钱  -不
- paying 2,000 in the garage. - No.
-天啊  不要  -不  我也不想这样
- Oh, God, no. - No, I'm not advocating for it.
只是...  这个就算了吧
I'm saying that's, you know... strike that.
好的  我会试试
Okay, so I'm just gonna, I'm gonna try
把徒步旅行业务多卖点钱
get a higher price for the business.
妈妈
Mom!
以圣父  圣子和圣灵的名义
In the name of the Father, the Son, the Holy Spirit.
神父  请宽恕我  我有罪
Forgive me father, for I have sinned.
柯克船长就是耶稣基督
Captain Kirk is Christ!
电视剧《星际迷航》中的一名虚构角色
以圣父  圣子...
In the name of the Father, the Son...
柯克船长就是耶稣基督
Captain Kirk is Christ!
"柯克船长就是耶稣基督"
"Captain Kirk is Christ."
别担心  我不是让你
Don't worry, I'm not asking you
违反告解的保密规则
to break the seal of confession.
我是在经堂外面听到的
I heard it from outside the oratory.
当时还有另一个年轻人在拍摄
There was another youth filming it.
-为什么  -老样子  为了社交媒体
- Why? - The usual: social media.
这不止是我们教区的问题
It's not just our parish.
我听其他牧师说
I've been hearing from other pastors
他们也面临一样的问题
that are dealing with the same thing.
神圣的主雕像被偷
Consecrated hosts being stolen.
还有这个
And this.
"赞扬流浪杰克"
"Praise Wandering Jack."
-这是什么意思  -不知道
- What's that? - No idea.
我在网上查不到任何相关的信息
I can't find anything about it online,
一些家长给学校打电话表示担心
and some parents are calling the school, worried about it.
让你的评估员查一查吧
Just have your assessors look into it.
-查什么  -这些网络流行语
- Look into what? - This meme.
这是在亵渎上帝
This... blasphemy.
只是些小孩子
It's just kids.
这些流行会自己消失
It dies out on its own.
也可能像《瘦长鬼影》那样
Or it's Slender Man.
恐怖片  4个女生受网络传说吸引
召唤瘦长男人后发生的一系列恐怖故事
圣安德烈高中的一个一年级新生上周自杀了
A freshman committed suicide last week at St. Andre's.
他父母认为他在网上被什么东西缠住了
His parents think he got caught up in something online.
好
Okay.
我听说维克托·莱孔特来过这里
I heard Victor LeConte was here.
真的吗
Really?
他去找你了吗
Did he approach you?
我吗
Me?
没有
No.
他想干什么
What did he want?
不知道
No idea.
要是他接近你  请告诉我
Tell me if he approaches you.
好的
Certainly.
这东西叫什么来着
It's called what?
流浪杰克
Wandering Jack.
应该是网上的某个流行语
It's supposedly some Internet meme.
这里没有血了
Well, there's no blood.
妈妈  刚刚这里都是血
Mom, it was all blood before.
现在没有了
Well, it's gone now.
你们俩在干什么
What are you two doing?
我们在打扫厕所
Oh, um, we're working on my toilet.
这是附身还是...
So, this is a possession or...
一个朋友来电
我不知道
I don't know, uh...
我晚点再打给你  我得接个电话
I-I'll call you back. I got to get this.
你好
Hello?
我看看水管
I'll take a look at the pipes.
那里可能有堵塞
You might have something clogged up there.
没事  我可以请一个水管工
That's okay, I can just call a plumber.
可你不是说你请不起水管工
Wait, but I thought you said you couldn't afford a plumber,
-因为我们...  -劳拉
- because we... - Oh, Laura.
我明天来看看
I'll take a look tomorrow.
大卫打电话有什么事吗
What did, uh, David call about?
有个网络流行语叫...
Um, this thing online called...
流浪杰克  吹口哨杰克
Wandering Jack, Whistling Jack...
-"来访杰克"吗  -什么
- Visiting Jack? - What?
那个流行语叫"来访杰克"
The meme's called Visiting Jack.
等等  这是什么意思
Wait, wait, what is this?
网上很流行这么玩
It's this thing on the Internet
你念他的名字三次时...
where you say his name three times...
不  不  如果你在晚上看到他
No, no, if when you see him at night
-如果是个月满之夜  -没错
- if there's a full moon. - Yeah.
你朋友雷不是看到过吗
I thought your friend saw it, Ren.
闭嘴
Shut up.
别让她闭嘴
Hey, don't say shut up.
雷是谁
Who's Ren?
圣安德烈高中的一个学生
Someone from St. Andre's!
琳在跟这个男孩约会
It's a boy that Lynn's dating.
没有...我没有在跟谁约会
I'm not... I'm not dating anyone.
不  我没有  别说了  我没有...
No, I'm not! Stop! I'm not...
好  好了  别说了  别说了
Okay, okay, hey, hold on, hold on!
这个男孩看到了什么
What did this boy see?
"来访杰克"是怎么回事
What's Visiting Jack?
对一些人来说  死亡是恐惧的来源
Death is a source of dread for some.
对另一些人来说  它被认为是一个人从情感
For others, it is perceived as a release from one's emotional
或身体痛苦中得到的释放
or physical suffering.
在许多宗教中  死亡根本不是生命的终结
In many religions, death is not the end of life at all,
而是通往新事物的大门
but rather a gateway to something new.
也许会引向对一个人的性格和道德选择的
Perhaps leading to the ultimate judgement of one's
为死亡的必然性做准备
最终判断
character and moral choices.
不管你如何看待死亡  事实上
However you interpret death, the fact is,
它都是生命中必然的一部分
it is an inevitable part of life.
因此...
Because of this...
你好  雷诺德
Hi, Renold.
我是克里斯汀·布沙尔德
I'm Kristen Bouchard.
教区派我来
I've been sent by the parish to
看看你怎么样
see how you're doing.
雷
Hey, Ren.
她是我妈妈
This is my mom.
她想帮助你
She wants to help.
一切还好吗
Is everything all right?
...我引以为傲的是什么
...that I'm proud of?
我为之后悔的是什么
What are some things that I regret?
他已经这样五天了
He's been in there for five days.
我唯一能和他说话的方式就是视频聊天
The only way I can even talk to him is over video chat.
你不知道这是怎么回事吗
And you have no idea what this is about?
不知道
No.
他只是说  "他找上我了"
He just says, "He's coming for me."
就这一句话  不断地重复
That's it. Over and over.
我能跟他聊聊吗
Can I talk to him?
-你可以试试  -好
- You can try. - Okay.
不  还是我来吧
No, uh, let me, let me take it.
只有我一个人会好些
Better if I'm alone.
嗨  雷
Hey, Ren,
你还好吗
How you doing?
琳  只有我们两个人吗
Lynn, is it just us?
是的
Yeah.
我喜欢你的房间
I liked your room.
很酷
It was cool.
等你父母走后我还想看看你的屋子
I still want to see your room when your parents are gone.
你什么时候出来
So, when are you coming out?
我不知道
I don't know.
我还没做完
I'm not done.
做完什么
Done with?
任务
The licks.
什么任务
What licks?
我不知道那是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
我不能告诉你  琳
I can't tell you, Lynn.
为什么  我什么都跟你说
Why not? I tell you everything.
因为它会杀死我
Because it'll kill me.
这跟"来访杰克"有关系吗
Is this about Visiting Jack?
琳  告诉我你没看它  对吧
Lynn, you didn't look at it, did you?
为什么我不能看它
Why shouldn't I?
天呐  你什么时候看到的
Oh, fuck, when did you look?
昨天
Y-yesterday.
琳  你还有六天
Lynn, you have six days.
-你要马上开始才行  -不然呢
- You got to get started now. - Or?
它会杀死你和你全家
It'll kill you and your family.
你拿到的是什么任务
What lick are you on?
我还  我还没开始
I haven't s-started yet.
琳  上线  快去领任务
Lynn, go online, get it now.
你要在七天内做完七个任务  不然就会死
You have seven licks in seven days or you're dead.
我去哪里找任务
Where do I find the licks?
你从哪里看到的图片就去哪里找
The same place that you looked at the photo.
你是从哪里看到的
Where did you look at it?
你没看它吧
You-you didn't look at it, did you?
-雷  -琳  别去看它
- Ren... - Lynn, do not look at it, okay?
它会把你拖入地狱
It'll drag you to hell.
就像学校里的韦恩那样
Like Wayne from school.
他们说他吞枪自杀了  但其实是"来访杰克"干的
They said he shot himself, but it was Visiting Jack.
近期横跨五区的离奇火灾时间线
好  我现在去查看他的浏览器历史记录
Okay, I'm gonna check his browser history.
你认识这个自杀的孩子韦恩吗
Do you know this kid, Wayne, who committed suicide?
不认识
No.
他在圣安德烈高中上学
He goes to St. Andre's.
他用他爸爸的枪自杀了
He shot himself with his dad's gun.
我们为此举办过祷告会
We had a prayer assembly about it.
你认得这个地址吗
Do you recognize this address?
不认识
No.
他去过这个地方吗
Has he ever gone to this address?
没有  他放学后都直接回家
No. He comes right home after school.
你认得吗
Do you recognize it?
不认得
No.
妈妈  我不认得
Mom, I don't.
我想到一个方法
Okay, one thought.
斯坦威街54号
Hmm, 54 Steinway.
斯坦威街56号
56 Steinway.
58号  街对面
58... across the street...
这里
There.
楼上有什么
What's upstairs?
警告
此地址应用户要求被屏蔽
"来访杰克"吗
Visiting Jack?
或许我们本来就不应该看它
Maybe we shouldn't be looking at this anyway.
雷说别看
Ren said not to.
琳
Lynn.
你应该知道这是假的吧
You know it's just make-believe, right?
人们以恐吓他人为乐而已
People enjoy scaring each other, that's it.
我知道  但是
I know, but...
或许我们就不应该看它
maybe we shouldn't be looking anyway.
所以我做错了什么
So what am I doing wrong?
你没有做错什么  你只是不够聪明而已
You're not doing anything wrong, you're just not that smart.
-谢谢你啊  -让开
- Thank you. - Just get out of my way.
我们用网站时光机就好了
We just use the Wayback Machine.
我试过了
I already did that.
那你没有用过进阶版
You didn't use the Wayback
-网站时光机  -别扯了
- Wayback Machine. - Really? Come on.
这是我自己写的应用程序
An app of my own creation.
然后我们就可以找到
And we'll find--
看好了
let's see--
一份更早的迭代
an even earlier iteration.
好了
There.
看吧
Ta-da.
看来有人真的很不希望你
Someone really doesn't want you to see
看到楼上的窗户里有什么
what's in that upstairs window.
嗯
Yeah, well...
这是个诅咒
there's a curse.
一个诅咒
A curse?
-你认真的吗  -是的
- Really? - Yeah.
如果你看到  你就得在七天里
If you see it you have to perform seven tasks
完成七个任务  不然它就会杀了你
in seven days or it'll kill you.
-你做这份工作还能拿钱吗  -相信我
- And you get paid for this job? - Believe me,
这甚至不是这个月发生的最离奇的事情
it's not even the strangest thing this month.
你还想看看它
Well, do you still want to see it
还是我们就不管它了
or should we let it go?
继续看看
Yeah, go.
挖深一层
Okay, one level deeper.
这是什么
Mm, what is that?
进阶进阶版
The Wayback, Wayback,
-网站时光机吗  -嘘
- Wayback Machine? - Shh.
好了
Okay, here we go.
一份更早的迭代
One more iteration.
-有了  -真不错
- There. - Mmm, nice.
我感觉被诅咒了
I'm feeling cursed.
靠
Fuck.
《恐怖事物立体书》
流行语恶魔
邪恶
第三季第二集
早上好
Morning.
你好
Hi.
利兰  我  我来这里做什么
Leland, what-what am I doing here?
我们在工作
We're working.
什么样的工作
What-what kind of work?
可以让你住上新房的工作
The work that will pay for your new home.
那种能让你外孙女都住得下的大房子
The new home that will keep your grandkids near.
你好
Oh. Hi.
这是你的工作
This is your job.
你需要让人们不停浏览负面消息
You're to keep the people doomscrolling.
使他们专注于电脑里的东西
Keep them glued to their computer.
让他们会看到新的政治斗争
So they're reading about the new political fight
参议院投票权立法停滞不前
国内恐怖主义
经济状况
or the economy
股票市场崩溃
三大指标纷纷跌至谷底  科技股遭受重创
全球变暖和疫情
or global warming, plagues.
病毒释放
全球变暖可能会释放出古老的病毒病原体
从而导致地球上所有人类的死亡
-所以我们还能控制疫情了  -不
- So we control plagues? - No.
是地狱之父在掌控
The father below controls plagues.
但我们掌控大众应对负面消息的方式
But we control how people react to plagues.
目前  那才是一切
And these days, that is everything.
几个世纪之前  80%由路西法控制
Centuries ago, it was 80% Lucifer,
20%的人是他的追随者
and 20% his followers.
如今情况正好相反
Now that's been reversed.
所以  基本来说
So, basically,
-我是个在网络上恶意挑衅的人  -嘿
- I'm a troll. - Hey,
恶意挑衅也是个光荣的职位
trolling is an honored profession.
他们就像是地狱之父棋盘上的骑士
Trolls are the knights of the father's chessboard.
我只是觉得黑暗的力量
I guess I just thought the powers of darkness
会更...黑暗
would be more, you know... dark.
的确黑暗
It is dark.
杀人  夺走他们的孩子
Kill people, take their children,
你冒着他们向上帝求助的风险
you run the risk of them turning to God.
-我不信上帝  -那也是个好事
- I don't believe in God. - And a good thing, too.
但若人们遭受太多不幸  就会向上帝求助
But if give people too much tragedy, they'll turn to Him.
你想让他们一直担忧  无束缚
You want to keep them nervous, unbound,
专注于世界上所有
focusing on all the bad things
不幸的事
in the world.
浏览负面消息
Doomscrolling.
聚焦邪恶
Where the focus is evil,
而非美好
and not good.
我每天会给你一个任务
Every day I'm gonna bring you a mission.
你会想质疑这些任务
You're gonna want to question these missions.
但你不能
But you can't.
也不会
You won't.
因为这就是你的工作
It's your job.
做吧
Do it.
难道我们不该等等看有没有闪电吗
Shouldn't we wait for lightning?
这还不够恐怖
It's not quite spooky enough.
我说我们明天早上再来
I said that we'd come back tomorrow morning,
但神父不同意
but Father overruled me.
-我还有弥撒  -那我们的想法是
- I have mass. - So, what are we thinking?
这是一栋待售的废弃房子
Uh, it's an abandoned house up for resale.
打扮成恶魔的孩子们闯入了
Kids broke into it with a demon costume.
-为什么  -为了博眼球
- Why? - To clout chase.
他们肯定知道
They had to know
街景摄像机
that the street view camera
正好在...
was coming by exactly at the...
楼上有什么东西
There's something up there.
-现在吗  -是的
- Now? - Yeah.
我什么都没看见
I don't see anything.
你去哪
Where you going?
我要去确认一下
I'm gonna go check it out.
一个朋友
抱歉  我要先接一下电话
I'm sorry, I-I have to take this.
你好
Hello?
主之意志
Is est a Deo habetur.
我现在有事
I'm in the midst of something.
麦迪逊街2201号
2201 Madison.
你有20分钟时间
You have 20 minutes.
门把手上有一个黑色胶带
There is a doorknob with black masking tape on it.
扭开  上楼
Turn it, go up the stairs.
20分钟内我赶不到  我...
I can't in 20 minutes. I...
麦迪逊街2201号
2201 Madison.
20分钟
Twenty...
我们可以明天再来吗
Hey, uh, can we come back tomorrow?
我有事要走
I have to go.
-什么  你去哪  -工作
- What? Where? - Work.
-我们可以明天再来确认  -不行
- We'll do this tomorrow. - No.
因为现在在里面的人  明天可能就不在了
'Cause whoever's in there will be gone tomorrow.
你待在这  若我15分钟内没回来  就报警
Look, stay here. If I'm not back in 15 minutes, call the police.
别跟上去  好吧
Don't follow him, okay?
我先走了
Um, I got to go.
有任何事发生
Call me if there's...
尽管打给我
anything.
大卫  你没什么事吧
David, is everything all right?
没事
I think so.
好吧  这是明智之举
Okay, this is smart.
怎么了
What?
你看到了什么
What did you see?
走吧
Let's go.
刚那是什么
What was that?
可能是某种动物留下的
It could be from some animal.
有人吗
Hello?
你是谁
Who are you?
菲比斯
Phoebus.
你又是谁
Who are you?
-你在这干什么  -我住在这
- What are you doing here? - I live here.
-你非法占用吗  -我不太喜欢这种说法
- You're squatting? - I don't like that word.
美国有1390万套空房屋
There are 13.9 million empty homes in the United States,
我只需要一间
and I needed one.
我没了奖学金  负担不起住宿舍的钱
I lost my scholarship and I can't afford the dorms.
好吧  有人在窗户边看到了你
Yeah, well, someone saw you in the window,
然后他们认为你是"来访杰克"
and then they thought you were Visiting Jack.
你也见到他了吗
You've seen him, too?
你想告诉我
You want to tell me that...
这不是你吗
this is not you, hmm?
不  那是"来访杰克"
No, that's Visiting Jack.
只要我为他提供食物  他就让我住在这
He lets me stay here as long as I feed him.
所以你也见到他了吗
So you've seen him, too?
不  我只听过他的声音
No, I hear him.
我让这里保持黑暗  因为他喜欢黑暗
I keep it dark in here. He likes the dark.
并且我需要按时为他提供食物
And I have to be on time with the food.
这是你写的吗
This your handwriting?
七个任务
对  但是他让我写下来的
Yeah, but he told me to write them down...
胡扯  你就是"来访杰克"
Yeah, bullshit! You're Visiting Jack.
-我不是  -你知道有人因为你的胡话
- I'm not. - You know, someone committed suicide
自杀了吗  混蛋
because of your bullshit, asshole?
不是我  我不是  嘿  别拍我
Not mine. I'm not. Hey, hey, hey, stop!
你要干嘛  叫"来访杰克"来吗
What are you gonna do, call Visiting Jack?
出去  出去  出去  出去
Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out!
你没戴罗马领
You're not wearing your collar.
-什么  -小声点
- What? - Keep your voice low.
你需要向前一点
You'll have to lean in.
你没戴罗马领
You're not wearing your collar.
我通常不戴
I-I don't, uh, usually.
会吸引别人注意
It, uh, draws attention.
戴上
Wear it.
之后你会收到一通电话
You will receive a call telling you
让你去送这个
where to deliver this.
-圣经吗  -对
- A Bible? - Yes.
别打开
Don't open it.
这合法吗
Is this legal?
根据哪个国家的法律
According to the laws of which country?
这个国家
This one.
你有疾病祈祷的随身包吗
Do you have a sick call traveling case?
-有  -带上
- Yes. - Carry it.
几天内  你会受到电话
Within a few days, you'll receive a call
告诉你去哪里送圣经
telling you where to deliver that Bible.
可能是酒店房间
It might be a hotel room.
可能是公车站
It might be a bus stop.
随身带着
Keep it with you at all times.
戴上罗马领
Wear a collar.
把东西送到
And deliver it.
我不明白
I-I-I don't understand.
我看见他了  我看见"来访杰克"了
I saw him. I-I saw Visiting Jack.
不  那只是有个人
No. It was, it was a guy dressed
打扮成恶魔的样子  吓跑别人
in a demon outfit to scare people away.
-你怎么知道  -我妈去找这个人了
- Well, how do you know that? - My mom went to the guy.
他是个流浪的大学生
He's a college student who's homeless
住在那栋房子里
and just staying at this house.
-但那些任务呢  -都是他自己想的
- But the licks? - He made them all up.
他只是想得到点赞
He's just trying to get upvotes.
看
Look.
就是他
Here he is.
瞧
See?
他就是个大学生
He's just some college kid.
你在害怕空气  雷
You're scared of nothing, Ren.
-出来吧  -你看照片了吗
- Come on out. - Did you look at the picture?
-什么照片  -来访杰克的
- What picture? - Of Visiting Jack.
看到了  只是服装
Yeah. It's just a costume.
那其他的房子呢
Well, what about the other houses?
什么房子
What houses?
还有其他六栋  他也在那里吗
The other six. Was he there, too?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
还有六栋其他房子
There were six other places.
"来访杰克"全都在那里
Visiting Jack was at all of them.
他杀了所有没做任务的家庭
And he killed every family that didn't do the tasks.
你妈妈也在  对吧
Your mom is there, too, isn't she?
让我见她
Let me see her.
雷  这家伙是个骗子
Ren, this guy's a scam artist.
他只是想操纵网上的孩子
He's just trying to manipulate kids online.
听着
Listen,
"来访杰克"不是真的
Visiting Jack is real.
你让琳看到他了
And you let Lynn see him.
现在她只剩五天了  救救她
Now she has five days. Help her.
-雷  他不是真的  -是真的
- Ren, he's not real. - Yes, it is real.
看看其他六栋房子
Look at the other six homes.
在哪里  我要怎么找到
Where are they? How can I find them?
雷  如果你想帮助我女儿
Ren, if you want to help my daughter,
你得说服我
you got to convince me.
他是怎么找到这些地方的
How did he find these?
-不知道  -他总泡在网上
- I don't know. - He's on the Internet a lot.
妈妈
Mom?
要不我去车里等吧
Maybe I'll wait in the car.
行
Okay, sure.
-我马上出来  -好
- I'll be out in a minute. - Okay.
那里
There.
还有其他人在这么干吗
Is somebody else doing this?
-或  -或什么
- Or...? - Or what?
不知道  这是真的吗
I don't know. Is it real?
看下一个地方
Try the next one.
有可能是P的
I mean, it could be Photoshop.
也或许是深度伪造
Or, you know, some kind of deepfake.
也许吧
Maybe.
你要怎么解释这个
How do you explain that?
给
Here we go.
你没有啤酒吗
You don't have a beer?
克里斯汀成箱的买这些
Kristen buys these by the case.
但现在我回来不走了
But now that I'm here permanently,
以后会换成啤酒
I'm gonna replace it with beer.
-干杯  -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我知道  你会习惯的
Yeah, I know, no. You get used to it.
怎么了
So, what's going on?
这个嘛
Well...
我需要把生意卖的价格更高些
I need more money for the business.
-我们说好了是八万五  -不
- We decided on $85,000. - No.
我们说的是这是个协商的起点
We decided that was a good starting point for negotiation.
我至少需要十一万
I'm gonna need $110,000 at least.
如果我告诉你
Well, what if I told you...
有人想一次性付钱买下
that there's somebody who wanted to pay
你的所有生意呢
full freight for the business?
是多少钱
What is full freight?
八十万
$800,000.
-开玩笑吧  -不是
- You're kidding. - No.
他们为什么要花这么多钱
Why would they pay that?
这个...这是新经济
That... it's the new economy.
-什么  -好吧  有些亿万富翁
- What? - Okay, some billionaire
想把我们的买卖规模化
wants to scale our business.
就是那种会买宇宙飞船的亿万富翁
It's like those spaceship billionaires.
这些日子所有人都喜欢冒险
Everybody's into adventure these days.
-谁  那人是谁  -一个风投者
- Who? Who is this person? - Some VC.
他想见你  他有一些问题
He-he wants to meet you. He's got some questions.
我现在突然很想知道
I have the sudden urge to bow.
阿科斯塔神父
Father Acosta.
很抱歉昨晚我抛下了你们
I'm sorry I abandoned you guys yesterday.
-有人快死了吗  -不是  只是工作
- Was somebody dying? - No. Just the job.
看起来你们解决了
So... sounded like you guys solved it.
对  但又遇到了新问题
Yeah, but then we ran into a snag.
嗯
Yeah.
这些好吓人
Yeah, these are pretty spooky.
我们还发现了其他东西
Yeah, so we just discovered something else.
我们只查了四栋房子  但目前为止
Yeah, we're only four houses in, but, so far,
这四栋房子都与凶案有关
these four are all connected to a murder.
或自杀  这对夫妇
Or suicide. This was a couple
在入室抢劫中被杀
that was, uh, killed in a home invasion.
这是纵火  三人死亡
This is arson-- three dead.
自杀  两人上吊
Suicide. Two hangings.
所以这些孩子故意挑选了这些
So the kids that did this just cherry-picked the houses
与暴力死亡有关的房子
that had violent deaths to make it look
让一切看上去像"来访杰克"干的
like Visiting Jack was culpable.
有可能  但问题还是
Yeah, probably, but the question remains...
他们是如何把"来访杰克"
how did they put Visiting Jack in each
嵌入这些街景图片中的
of these street-view pictures?
-看这张图片  -这怎么了
- How about this one? - What about it?
很难看到房子
Kind of hard to see the house.
对  但有人在车道上  你看
Yeah, but there's someone in the driveway. Look.
或许我们该问问她看到了什么
Maybe we should ask her what she saw.
好
Okay.
所以地址是...
So the address is...
在弗罗斯特大街
on Frost.
-怎么了  -那里几个月前发生了凶案
- What? - The violent crime occurred a few months ago.
-是...  -奥森·勒鲁
- It was... - Orson LeRoux.
是  没错
Yeah, it was, uh...
他在那里被杀的
where he was killed.
那我们去看别处的房子
Well, we should look at the other houses.
图片中是埃米莉  他的遗孀
This is Emily in the picture. It's his widow.
她继承了房子  我们可以去找她聊聊
She inherited the house. We should go talk to her.
-我们去就行  克里斯汀  -我们去  你不用...
- We can do that, Kristen... - We can do... You don't ha...
没事  我们走吧
No. Let's go.
来访杰克的七大任务
1.向牧师大喊"柯克船长是耶稣"
2.摧毁一件圣物
3.打老师脸一拳
4.与处子做爱
5.偷父母的酒  一口气喝完
6.在第13层楼的窗台上做13次开合跳
7.用剃刀在自己脸上刻下"杰克"
确保下刀够深流出血来
你是要拍一些照片还是干其他的...
I mean, do you have to take a picture or something...
你有多长时间
How long till you're,
-去完成这些任务  -周一之前
- like, done with it, like...? - Uh, until Monday.
你真觉得自己不做就会死吗
And you do you really think you'll be dead if you don't?
不  我就觉得这是个挑战
No, I just think it's a challenge,
做了总比不做好
so it's better to do it than not.
那放学后就去教堂
Then go to the church after school.
然后大喊"柯克船长是耶稣"吗
And shout "Captain Kirk is Christ"?
他们会认出我的
They'll know it's me.
那就去难看一些的基督教堂
Just, like, go to the Christian church, the ugly one.
也没说必须是天主教堂
They never said it had to be Catholic.
其他任务是什么
What are the other tasks?
2.摧毁一件圣物
3.打老师脸一拳
4.与处子做爱
我要打一名老师
I have to hit a teacher.
-如果这是个玩笑呢  -你什么意思
- What if it's a joke? - What do you mean?
用这个打老师
Hit a teacher with this.
你就像这样打一拳...
You just, like, punch...
对  打年长的老师然后哈哈大笑
Oh, yeah, hit the old one and then laugh.
-就会像在开玩笑  -我能看下任务清单吗
- It'll be like a joke. - Can I see the list?
-不行  -为什么
- No, no, no, no. - Why?
有些少儿不宜
They're not all for kids.
比如呢
Like what?
比如  我要从爸妈那里偷酒喝掉
Like, I have to steal alcohol from Mom and Dad and drink it.
没有那么少儿不宜啊
That's not so bad.
少一瓶玛格丽特妈妈不会发现  走吧  行动
Mom won't miss a margarita. Come on, let's go.
-要是有那么简单...  -快点  走吧  琳
- I mean, if it's that easy... - Come on, let's go, Lynn.
他迟到了
He's late.
他有八十万美金  有迟到的资本
He has $800,000. He can afford to be late.
-别别别  孩子们  -你们非要下来不可吗
- Hey, no, no, no, no. Guys. - Do you have to be here?
我们要拿牛奶  拜托
We're getting some milk, come on!
好  快点  去楼上喝
Okay, real quick, but drink it upstairs. Okay.
不行  爸爸  妈妈说
No, Dad, Mom says
-不准在楼上喝东西  -他来了
- no drinks upstairs. - He's coming on!
加入会议
好  你们待在厨房  安静点
Okay, stay in there. Just be quiet.
玛格丽特
没事的  喝吧
It's fine, just do it.
-琳  喝吧  -我给你打开
- Lynn, just do it. - I'll open it for you.
不用  我来开
No, I got it.
快  像妈妈一样一口气喝光
Come on, chug it like Mom.
她不会发现的
She won't even notice it.
好
Okay.
-你喝了  -天啊
- You're doing it. - Oh, my gosh.
真是疯了
You're crazy.
-你竟然真喝了  -天啊
- I can't believe you did it. - Oh, my God.
你做到了
You did it!
抱歉  埃迪  我没听清
sorry, Eddie, I didn't quite catch that.
我说  在我其他的生意中
I said, in my other businesses,
有一点很关键
there has always been one key.
跟着创始人亲身实践学习
To learn hands-on from the originator.
抱歉  我没太明白
I'm sorry, I don't quite follow.
我要你和我一起去尼泊尔
I need you to go with me to Nepal.
把你的生意详尽地讲给我
Show me the ins and outs of your business.
先生  巴什可以与您同去
Oh, sir, no, um, Bash can do that.
我不会再去尼泊尔了
I have taken my last trip to Nepal.
为什么  我不该投资尼泊尔吗
Why? Why, should I not be investing in Nepal?
不是  我已经成家了  先生
No, no. It's just that I have a family, sir.
而且...很久没陪家人了
And, um... I've already been away for so long.
尽管我非常理解  先生
Well, as much as I sympathize, sir.
但我要出八十万美金
I am offering to buy your business
收购你的公司
for $800,000.
-答应他  混蛋  快同意  -我唯一的要求
- Say yes, fucker, say yes. - And all I require is for you
-你带我去熟悉一下  -先生  恕我直言
- to show me the ropes. - Uh, sir, with respect,
巴什能带您去
Bash can do that
跟我和您去没差别
just as well as I can.
是这样  安迪
Here is the thing, Andy.
当我心有所属
When I know what I want,
就势在必得  所以...
I know what I want, so...
我愿意在
I am willing to pay you
付你八十万的基础上
a $150,000 surcharge
再加十五万美金作为你的服务费
on top of my $800,000 for your services.
不是付给巴什
Not Bash's services.
是作为你带我去尼泊尔的酬劳
Your services to guide me to Nepal.
这是我的底线了
And that is my bottom line.
先生
Uh, sir?
埃迪  我能...
Eddie, can I...?
我能...一会给您回电吗
Can I call... Let me call you back.
我要和我的日子商量下...
I just need to check in with my, uh, my life...
和我妻子商量下
with my wife.
当然  但明日要给我答复
Certainly, but I need to know by tomorrow,
否则我就另寻他处了
or I am moving on.
天啊  他真的不想去
Boy, he really doesn't want to go.
对  但是克里斯汀更务实
Yeah, Kristen's the practical one.
她会劝他去的
She'll make him go.
感觉像是和名人同行
It's like being with a celebrity.
对  一个惹人厌的名人
Yeah, a really hated celebrity.
我...
I...
一位朋友
来电
我得接个电话
I have to take this.
好  你去吧
Okay, go ahead.
你好
Hello?
你其实不必这么做的
You know, you don't have to do this.
做什么
Do what?
来勒鲁的房子
The LeRoux house.
没事  我很好
Oh, no, I'm good.
他最近神秘兮兮的
He's been very mysterious lately.
是的  他现在可是牧师兄弟会的人
Yeah, he's in the priest frat now.
你俩之间没什么问题吧
There's nothing weird between the two of you, right?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
自从他成为一位牧师之后
Well, just, since he became a priest,
你们就...
you have been...
相处得很不自然
awkward around each other.
不  没有  我们没事
No, no, no. We-We're good.
我们只是没什么机会
We, we just haven't had much of a chance
在一起相处  所以...
to spend any time together, so...
珀西瓦尔酒店  2102号房间
Hotel Percival. Room 2102.
-什么时候  -现在
- When? - Now.
我离那里有40分钟路程
I-I'm 40 minutes away.
不  是25分钟  现在就走
No, you're 25. Leave now.
我是就把《圣经》放在房间里吗
And I'm just leaving the Bible in the room?
不  计划有变
No, change of plan.
2102号房间有个人快要死了
There's a man dying in Room 2102.
你说你是迈克尔神父来执行临终宗教仪式
Say you're Father Michael and administer the last rites.
听懂我说的了吗
Did you understand what I said?
为什么由我来执行临终宗教仪式
Why am I administering last rites?
因为他快死了  而且电话打给了你
Because he's dying and you've been called.
执行结束后  你要在房间里
After you're done, you'll find a postcard
找到一张明信片
somewhere in the room.
带上它离开
Take it and leave.
但要确保你离开时门开着
But make sure you leave the door open.
大卫
David?
这太疯狂了
This is crazy.
你需要我重复某个部分吗
Do you need me to repeat any part of it?
我没听到那句拉丁语
I didn't hear the Latin.
主之意志
Is est a Deo habetur.
20分钟
20 minutes.
好了  你准备好去看看了吗
Okay, you ready to go?
实际上  我得去忙了
Actually, I've just gotten called away.
什么  现在吗
What? Now?
是的
Yes.
去哪
Where?
说来话长
It's a long story.
我晚点找你们吧
I'll talk to you two later?
有事不对劲
Uh, something is up.
没错
Yep.
好吧
Okay.
准备好了吗
Ready?
好了
Yeah.
再次见到你很高兴  克里斯汀
It's good to see you again, Kristen.
生活不容易
It's been hard.
我了解
I know.
我听说你有新欢了
I heard you met someone.
一位非常可爱的人
A very sweet man.
他让我更容易回到这里
He made it easier coming back here.
这里是...
This is...
奥森遇害的地方...
where Orson was when he...
起初警方认为是我干的
At first the police thought that I did it.
我听说了
I heard about that.
他们至今没有弄清楚到底发生了什么
They still haven't figured out what's happened.
你看过你家的那个街景吗  勒鲁太太
Have you seen the street view of your house, Ms. LeRoux?
什么东西
The what?
对  我听说过这个
Oh, yeah, I heard about this.
一个鬼魂  是吗
A ghost, right?
是的  那么...
Yeah, so, uh...
我们认为那个下车的人是你
we think that that's you there, getting out of your car.
我们想知道你是不是看到了什么人
We just wondered if you saw someone
装扮成那样  或者...
in a costume or...
有人故意拍这种照片吗
someone setting up this shot?
这个鬼魂照吗
This ghost shot?
没有
No.
但是有些怪事
There was something weird, though.
那个司机  街景里面的司机
The driver-- the street view driver--
他们的车很奇怪  车顶有相机
their car is so weird, with the camera on the roof.
开车经过那幢房子三次
Drove past the house three times.
倒回去  再开
Back up, do it again.
你知道原因吗
Do you know why?
不知道  不清楚
No, I have no idea.
我们怎么看
What are we thinking?
我认为有人和街景司机协同工作
I'm thinking somebody is working with the street view driver.
这样一来  他们知道那辆车要来了
That is how they knew that the car was coming.
七个住所都是吗
With all seven residences?
-对  -那我们怎么找出
- Yeah. - So how do we find out
这个街景司机是谁呢
who this street view driver was?
看这个
Watch this.
就是他
There he is.
珀西瓦尔酒店
我...我是迈克尔神父
I-I'm Father Michael.
你怎么还不明白
他马上就快死了
不  我不知道出了什么事
他一下子就躺倒了
我是来这执行临终宗教仪式的
I'm here to administer the last rites.
我不管你听到了什么
他在飞机上还好好的
出事了  但我不知道究竟是怎么回事
借此神圣膏油  愿主
With this holy anointing, may the Lord
以祂的爱与仁慈...
in His love and mercy...
《凯丽·赫本的家》
《卡内基音乐厅》
《麦基姆  米德  怀特  大师之作》
主以祂的爱与仁慈
...Lord in His love and mercy...
以圣神的恩宠助佑你
...help you with the grace of the Holy Spirit.
愿主赦免你的罪
May the Lord who frees you from sin
救赎你
save you
把你举高
and raise you up.
-不  不  亲爱的  -他死了
不要离开我们
你不能就这么走了
纽约  自由女神像
我能...帮上什么别的忙吗
May-may I help you with anything else?
先生  先生
不用不用
No, no.
进展如何
So, how'd it go?
嗯...
Well, um...
本发现那个出现在
Ben figured out that the street view driver was
七处恶魔住宅的街景司机
the same person at all seven houses
是同一个人  这家伙和我们
where this demon appeared, and the guy goes
找到的菲比斯上同一所学校  非全日制
to school part-time with the kid Phoebus that we found.
所以...他们是窜通好的
So... they concocted it together.
所以这是一个骗局
So it was a scam.
没错  社交媒体
Yep, social media
让动机变得又简单又愚蠢
makes motives both simpler and stupider.
那你的说来话长的事怎么样了
So, how'd your, uh, long story go?
-我的...  -你说的那是...
- My...? - Oh, you said it was a...
说来话长  你接了一通电话走了
a long story, you being called away?
弥撒时间表
Mass schedule.
总是必须要立刻解决
It always has to be solved, like, right then.
我怀念我们
I miss us.
这与我们无关
I-It had nothing to do with us.
我知道  但我们不再是从前的我们了
I know, but we're not what we were,
我觉得我...
and, and I think that I...
我觉得...
I think...
-我觉得是我造成的  -不是
- I think I caused that... - No.
当我找你忏悔时
...when I confessed to you
-然后之后的事  -克里斯汀
- and then afterwards. - Kristen,
没事
it's okay.
已经过去了
It's done.
显然没过去  因为如果过去了
Well, clearly it's not done, 'cause if it were done,
你依然会是我朋友  然而...
I'd still have a friend, and...
我能感觉到我不是
I can feel that I don't.
克里斯汀
Kristen,
我身上发生的事
what's going on with me
和我的...
has nothing to do with my...
我们的...
...with our...
和我们彼此的感情无关
Feelings toward each other?
对
Yes.
和我是牧师有关
It's to do with me being a priest.
一位新晋牧师
A new priest.
仅此而已
That's all.
我感觉很孤独
I feel lonely.
别这样
Don't be.
我在这里
I'm here.
我会重新做回自己
And I'll be myself again.
那就好
I'd like that.
我也觉得那挺好
I'd like that, too.
太好了
Great.
我们又是朋友了
Friends again.
明天见
I will see you tomorrow.
你回来迟了
You're late.
我不知道我还有时间限制
I didn't know I was on a schedule.
这是神圣的天主教堂
This is the holy Catholic Church.
你永远有时间限制
You're always on a schedule.
明信片呢
The postcard?
怎么了
What?
这是怎么回事
What was that?
什么怎么回事
What was what?
用圣事来掩盖你的间谍活动
Using the sacraments to cover your little espionage.
作为牧师  这是我第一次觉得自己像个骗子
This is the first time I felt like a fraud being a priest.
你当八天牧师以来的第一次吗
The first time in your eight days as a priest?
我的天啊
Oh, my goodness.
我在那里做什么
What was I doing there?
临终圣礼是你主持的吗
Did you administer the last rites?
是的
Yes.
只有这样我才能偷到这个
But only so I could steal this.
那个人要死了
That man was dying.
他为什么会死
Why was he dying?
大卫  你答应过梵蒂冈
David, you said yes to the Vatican.
-这份承诺会有负担  -不
- That yes came with a burden. - No.
他为什么会死
Why was he dying?
他被下毒了
He was poisoned.
为什么
Why?
有人企图阻止他
There was someone trying to prevent him
传递消息  那个消息
from delivering a message. That message.
这怎么能对抗魔鬼
How is this battling evil?
这一切在我看来无比邪恶
This all seems evil to me.
大卫
David...
作为评估员  在工作中
In your work as an assessor,
你必须发现两种来源的魔鬼
you must have found two sources of evil.
超自然和人类
The supernatural and the human.
我和人类打交道
I deal with the human.
行坏事的恶人
Bad people doing bad things.
邪恶的政府  杀人犯  刑讯者
Evil governments. Murderers. Torturers.
他们存在于这个世界  必须阻止他们
They exist in the world, and they must be stopped,
他们可能比恶魔还要多
maybe even more than demons.
这就是我需要那张明信片的原因
So that is why I need that postcard.
用来杀死另一位送信人吗
To kill another messenger?
不  为了救一个人
No. To save one.
谁
Who?
你想要这张明信片
You want this postcard,
我想知道我在救谁
I want to know who I'm saving.
格蕾丝·林
Grace Ling.
你认识她
You know her.
是你让我们注意到她的
You brought her to our attention.
梵蒂冈相信她是先知
The Vatican believes she is a prophet.
她被遣返回中国
She was deported back to China
在某个劳教所失踪
and lost in a work camp.
我们相信已找到她的位置
We believe we have located her,
那张明信片会告诉我们
and that postcard will tell us
是否有机会救回她
if there is a chance to recover her.
纽约
自由女神像
明信片
他们还给你其它什么了吗
Were you given anything else?
-没有  -你确定吗
- No. - Are you sure?
这个
This.
是小费
As a tip.
她在营地  周五离
干得好
Good work.
保持联系
We'll be in touch.
你爸说你喝了我一罐玛格丽特酒
Dad said you drank one of my margaritas.
我不希望你这样做
I don't want you doing that.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我看了那七个任务
I read the seven tasks.
"来访杰克"的任务
The Visiting Jack tasks.
我知道这是任务之一
I know it's one of them.
我不再相信那个了
I don't believe in that anymore.
任务四是"与处子做爱"
Task number four was "have sex with a virgin."
我还没到那一步  妈
I didn't get that far, Mom.
那雷呢
Did Ren?
我们没做爱
We didn't have sex.
没有
We didn't.
我想相信你  琳
I want to believe you, Lynn.
但你不能骗我
But you cannot lie to me.
我不会的
I won't.
是马桶的声音
That's the toilet.
我去处理
I'll get on it.
你考虑过吗
Have you thought about it?
然后呢
And?
这是你最后一次徒步旅行吗
This is your last trek?
是的
Yeah.
要去多久
And for how long?
三个月
Three months.
天啊
Oh, boy.
好吧
Well,
这确实是一大笔钱  而且
it's an insane amount of money, and...
我们需要用钱  所以我不...
...we need money, so I don't...
不知道我们该怎样拒绝
I don't really see how we can say no.
-我不想去  -我知道你不想
- I don't want to go. - I know you don't.
别死了
Just don't die.
好的
Okay.
预支一半的钱
And get half the money up front.
我们必须开始建那个卫生间
We have to start on that bathroom.
我会的
I will.
我非常爱你
I love you so much.
我也是
I love you, too.
做单亲妈妈实在太糟糕了
Being a single mom just really sucks.
我知道  我都知道
I know. I know.
就快结束了
It's almost over.
邪恶
第三季  第二集